EUGENIO BARROS

1122 N Clark St. Chicago, IL 60610 954-599-1311 eugenio barros18@hotmail.com

OBJECTIVE

General Manager equipped with extensive experience in all stages of running a business. Employs excellent leadership skills building and running teams of 40+ employees. Demonstrated ability to improve store operations, increase top line sales, reduce costs and maximize customer satisfaction.

WORK EXPERIENCE

08/2018 - current

Head Coach, Sweetgreen

Responsibilities:

- Recruit team members and managers. Motivate and coach employees to meet customer service, sales and profit goals.
- Comprehensive knowledge of operations.
- Developing systems to maximize efficiency.
- Maintain detailed reports of profitability information, customer and employee satisfaction.
- Work with vendors to ensure timely deliveries, quality product and accurate billing.

08/2014 - 08/2018

General Manager, Domino's Pizza, Medford-MA

Responsibilities:

- Recruit team members and managers.
 - Substantial knowledge of the logistic to provide timely deliveries.
- Developing systems to improve efficiency.
- Present data analysis of profitability, customer satisfaction.

EDUCATION

2019 - current

Information Technology, Bunker Hill Community College.

2001 - 2004

Brazilian Law School, Pontifical Catholic University of Goias.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Business development, customer service/revenue focused and problem solver.
- Team player and effective team builder.
- Develop and maintain relationship with partners and vendors.